Guide to the Jacques E. Levy Research Collection on Cesar Chavez
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Post Mortem Research, 1981-1997; Series VII; 4.40; (15 boxes)
  - WRITTEN COLLECTION
    - General Files
      - File 39. Cesar Chavez Obit, 1993-94 (Box 37, Folder 730)
      - File 40. Cesar Chavez Statement, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 731)
      - File 41. Chavez Family Interview DF Notes, 1994 Feb 18 (Box 37, Folder 732)
      - File 42. Chavez Family Interview Material, 1994 Feb 18 (Box 37, Folder 733-734)
      - File 43. Helen Chavez Fundraising Letter, 1993 Apr 30 (Box 37, Folder 735)
      - File 44. Jerome Cohen, 1981-95 (Box 37, Folder 736)
      - File 45. Eulogy for Juana Chavez, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 737)
      - File 46. FBI Files Correspondence, 1993-95, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 738)
      - File 47. Marshall Ganz, 1994, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 739)
      - File 48. Marshall Ganz Syllabus, 1994 (Box 37, Folder 740)
      - File 49. Marc Grossman, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 741)
      - File 50. W. C. Hartmire Forced Resignation, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 742)
      - File 51. Chris Hartmire Enneagram, 1994
      - File 52. Msgr. George Higgins, 1993, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 743)
      - File 53. Dolores Huerta, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 744)
      - File 54. Dolores Huerta and Richard Chavez (Box 38, Folder 745)
      - File 55. Giev Kashkooli, 1993-94 (Box 38, Folder 746-747)
      - File 56. Daniel Kingman, 1993-94, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 748)
      - File 57. Dr. Jerome Lackner, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 749)
      - File 58. JEL Book Outline, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 750)
      - File 59. JEL Tag Indexes (Box 38, Folder 751)
      - File 60. Philip Martin, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 752)
      - File 61. Medal of Freedom, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 753)
      - File 62. Judge Fred Metheny, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 754)
      - File 63. National Farm Worker Ministry, 1994-96 (Box 38, Folder 755)
      - File 64. Questions for Interviews, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 756)
      - File 65. Arturo Rodriguez Biography, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 757)
      - File 66. Ronald Reagan Library, 1993 Nov 23 (Box 38, Folder 758)
      - File 67. Fred Ross Eulogy, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 759)
      - File 68. Salinas Workers Retraction, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 760)
      - File 69. Sonoma County Peace Press, 1993 Jun (Box 38, Folder 761)
      - File 70. Synanon, 1997, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 762)
      - File 71. Timeline Chart, n.d.
      - File 72. UFW Constitutional Convention, 1994, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 763)
      - File 73. UFW Field Offices, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 764)
      - File 74. UFW Press Releases, 1992-93 (Box 38, Folder 765)
    - Oversized Files
      - File 75. Cesar Chavez Memorial Poster, [1993]
      - File 76. Dolores Huerta, 1988
      - File 77. Fred Ross Letters to CC, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 766)
      - Vol. 78. UFW Background & Chronology (Box 38, Folder 767)
      - File 79. PMR News Clippings, 1993-96, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 768-769)
        Stored also in: Oversize box 51, folder 975
      - File 80. JC on FBI Files, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 770)
      - File 81. FBI Files, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 771)
    - FBI
      - File 82. FBI Files pages 1-42, [1994] (Box 39, Folder 772)
      - File 83. FBI Files pages 43-128, [1994] (Box 39, Folder 773)
      - File 84. FBI Files pages 129-331, [1994] (Box 39, Folder 774)
      - File 85. FBI Files pages 332-470, [1994] (Box 39, Folder 775)
      - File 86. FBI Files pages 471-670, [1994] (Box 39, Folder 776)
      - File 87. FBI Files pages 671-906, [1994] (Box 40, Folder 777)
      - File 88. FBI Files pages 907-964, [1994] (Box 40, Folder 778)
      - File 89. FBI Files pages 965-1019, [1994] (Box 40, Folder 779)
      - File 90. FBI Files pages 1020-1162, [1994] (Box 40, Folder 780)
      - File 91. FBI Files pages 1163-1171, [1994] (Box 40, Folder 781)
      - File 92. FBI Files pages 1172-1421, [1994] (Box 40, Folder 782)
- Written Notes, 1968-1993; Series VIII; 0.84; (2 boxes)
  Series VIII, Written Notes, is organized into six subseries: Negotiations, Jacques Levy Personal Papers, Jacques Levy Correspondence, Jacques Levy Research Notes, Book and Movie Outline, and Post 1975 Materials. Within each subseries, the subject files are arranged alphabetically.
  - NEGOTIATIONS
    - File 1. Giumarra Negotiations, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 783)
    - Files 2-3. Negotiations with Fleming et al., n.d. (Box 41, Folder 784-785)
    - File 4. Negotiations with Fleming et al. 5/20/71 - 11/10/71, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 786)
  - JACQUES LEVY PERSONAL PAPERS
    - File 5. Book Tour, 1975-76 (Box 41, Folder 787)
    - File 6. Business Cards, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 788)
    - File 7. People for a Better Society, 1969 (Box 41, Folder 789)
    - File 8. JEL Speeches, 1976-77 (Box 41, Folder 790)
  - JACQUES LEVY CORRESPONDENCE
    - File 9. ATV Network Limited, 1973 Aug (Box 41, Folder 791)
    - File 10. Board of National Missions, 1970 Jun-Sep (Box 41, Folder 792)
    - File 11. Cesar Chavez, 1969-73 (Box 41, Folder 793)
    - File 12. Jim Drake, 1969 (Box 41, Folder 794)
    - File 13. International Repercussions to JEL Article, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 795)
    - File 14. Albert Kahn, 1969-70 (Box 41, Folder 796)
    - File 15. JEL Leave of Absence, 1969 Feb 6 (Box 41, Folder 797)
    - File 16. Literary Agents, 1969-93 (Box 41, Folder 798)
    - File 17. Permission Releases, 1975, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 799)
    - File 18. Mack & Diana Lyons, 1969-72 (Box 41, Folder 800)
    - File 19. Miscellaneous, 1970-73 (Box 42, Folder 801)
    - File 20. Senator George Murphy, 1969 Jun (Box 42, Folder 802)
    - File 21. Teamster Threat, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 803)
    - File 22. UFW Correspondence, 1970-73 (Box 42, Folder 804)
    - File 23. Wayne State University, 1969-70 (Box 42, Folder 805)
  - JACQUES LEVY RESEARCH NOTES
    - File 24. Biographic Notes, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 806)
    - File 25. Coachella March, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 807)
    - File 26. El Macriado, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 808)
    - File 27. Dolores Huerta Interview, 1969 Apr 5 (Box 42, Folder 809)
    - File 28. Coretta King, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 810)
    - File 29. Howard Marguleas, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 811)
    - File 30. Father Donald McDonnell, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 812)
    - File 31. Miscellaneous Working Notes, 1968-71, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 813)
    - File 32. Reagan Double-cross (Box 42, Folder 814)
    - File 33. Red Baiting, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 815)
    - File 34. Early Note Clipboard, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 816)
    - File 35. Grey Covered Clipboard, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 817)
  - BOOK AND MOVIE OUTLINE
    - File 36. Eagle Outline, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 818)
    - File 37. Film Outlines, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 819)
  - POST 1975 MATERIALS
    - File 38. JEL Contacts with CC in Late 80s (Box 42, Folder 820)
    - File 39. Request for Movie in '80s, 1988-89 (Box 42, Folder 821)
    - File 40. Chavez Lecture Transcripts, 1992 May-Jun (Box 42, Folder 822)
- Levy Inventory, Date: [1998]; Series IX; 0.21; (1 box)
  Series IX, Levy Inventory, is the original list created by Levy that accompanied the collection when it was acquired by the Beinecke Library.
  - Original Levy inventory, [1998] (Box 43, Folder 823-826)
- Assassination Plot, 1971-1974; Series X; 2.65; (9 boxes)
  Series X, Assassination Plot, is currently restricted. For further information, contact the curator. The series is organized into seven subseries: Audiotapes, Book Material, Plot Files, Plot Material, Shears Tapes, "The Snitch", and Transcripts. The subject files in the Book Material, Plot Files, Plot Material, and Transcripts subseries are arranged alphabetically.
  Boxes 71-73 contains audiovisual material. Restricted fragile. Reference copies are available upon request. Consult Access Services for further information.
  - AUDIOTAPES
    - Cassette sides 1-2. Larry Shears phone conversations, 1971 September 19-20; 1 (Box 71, Item barcode 39002104887857)
      Transcript: File 43, stored in: box 48, folder 923
    - Cassette sides 3-4. Larry Shears phone conversations, 1971; 1 (Box 71, Item barcode 39002104887865)
    - Cassette sides 5-6. Larry Shears phone conversations, 1971; 1 (Box 71, Item barcode 39002104887873)
    - Cassette sides 7-8. Larry Shears phone conversations, undated; 1 (Box 71, Item barcode 39002104887881)
      Transcript: File 43, stored in: box 48, folders 924
    - Cassette sides 9-10. Larry Shears phone conversations, undated; 1 (Box 71, Item barcode 39002104887899)
      Transcript for #9: File 43, stored in: box 48, folder 924. Cassette side 10 is blank
    - Cassette sides 11-12. Larry Shears phone conversations, undated; 1 (Box 71, Item barcode 39002104887907)
      Only 2:48 minutes. Transcript for #11 (incomplete): File 43: stored in: box 48, folders 924. Cassette side 12 is blank
    - Cassette sides 13-14. Larry Shears phone conversations, 1971 October 27; 1 (Box 71, Item barcode 39002104887915)
      Transcript: File 43, stored in: box 48, folder 924. Cassette side 14 is blank
    - Cassette sides 15-16. Larry Shears phone conversations, 1971 October 29; 1 (Box 71, Item barcode 39002104887923)
      Transcript for #15: File 43, stored in: box 48, folder 924. Cassette side 16 is blank
    - Cassette sides 17-18. Larry Shears statement on purpose of audiotape and explanation of conspiracy, and taped phone conversation, undated; 1 (Box 71, Item barcode 39002104887931)
      Side 17 is a test side with no information or transcript. Transcript for cassette 18: File 43, stored in: box 48, folder 924
    - Cassette sides 19-20. Larry Shears phone conversations, undated; 1 (Box 71, Item barcode 39002104887949)
      Transcript: File 43, stored in: box 48, folder 925
    - Cassette sides 21-22. Larry Shears phone conversations, [1971 September]; 1 (Box 71, Item barcode 39002104887956)
      Transcript: File 43, stored in: box 48, folder 925. Side 22 is recorded pop music
    - Cassette sides 23-24. Larry Shears phone conversations, undated; 1 (Box 71, Item barcode 39002104887964)
    - Cassette sides 25-26. Larry Shears phone conversations, undated; 1 (Box 71, Item barcode 39002104887972)
    - Cassette sides 27-28. Larry Shears phone conversations, undated; 1 (Box 71, Item barcode 39002104887980)
      Transcript: File 44, stored in: box 48, folder 926
    - Cassette sides 29-30. Larry Shears phone conversations with John Tudor. (1 of 2 copies), undated; 1 (Box 71, Item barcode 39002104887998)
      Transcript: File 44, stored in: box 48, folder 926. The first minute of side 30 are instructions on using a tape recorder. 2nd copy is labeled "John Tudor"
    - Cassette side 29-30 Larry Shears phone conversations with John Tudor (2 of 2 copies), undated; 1 (Box 71, Item barcode 39002104888004)
      Transcript: File 44, stored in: box 48, folder 926. The first minute of side 30 are instructions on using a tape recorder.
    - Cassette sides 31-32. Larry Shears phone conversations with Richard Pedigo. (1 of 2 copies), undated; 1 (Box 71, Item barcode 39002104888012)
      Transcript: File 44, stored in: box 48, folders 926-927. Transcript marked 31 is for cassette 32, and vice versa. The first two minutes of 32 is pop music. 2nd copy labeled "Richard Pedigo"
    - Cassette sides 31-32 Larry Shears phone conversations with Richard Pedigo. (2 of 2 copies), undated; 1 (Box 71, Item barcode 39002104888020)
      Transcript: File 44, stored in: box 48, folders 926-927. Transcript marked 31 is for cassette 32, and vice versa. The first two minutes of 32 is pop music.
    - Cassette sides 33-34. Larry Shears phone conversations. (1 of 2 copies), undated; 1 (Box 72, Item barcode 39002104888038)
      Transcript: File 44, stored in: box 48, folder 927. 2nd copy labeled "Crock on contractor"
    - Cassette sides 33-34. Larry Shears phone conversations. (2 of 2 copies), undated; 1 (Box 72, Item barcode 39002104888046)
      Transcript: File 44, stored in: box 48, folder 927.
    - Cassette sides 35-36. Larry Shears phone conversations. (1 of 2 copies), August; 1 (Box 72, Item barcode 39002104888053)
      Transcript: File 44, stored in: box 48, folders 927. 2nd copy labeled "Richard to [Aften?]"
    - Cassette sides 35-36. Larry Shears phone conversations. "Richard to offer..." (2 of 2 copies), August; 1 (Box 72, Item barcode 39002104888061)
      Transcript: File 44, stored in: box 48, folders 927.
    - Cassette sides 37-38. Larry Shears phone conversations. (1 of 2 copies), undated; 1 (Box 72, Item barcode 39002104888079)
      Transcript: File 44, stored in: box 48, folder 928. 2nd copy labeled "[700 Buy?]"
    - Cassette sides 37-38. Larry Shears phone conversations. (2 of 2 copies), undated; 1 (Box 72, Item barcode 39002104888087)
      Transcript: File 44, stored in: box 48, folder 928.
    - Cassette sides 39-40. Larry Shears narration and phone conversations. (1 of 2 copies), July; 1 (Box 72, Item barcode 39002104888095)
      Transcript: File 44, stored in: box 48, folder 928. 2nd copy labeled "Night of Bust"
    - Cassette sides 39-40. Larry Shears narration and phone conversations. "Night of Bust..." (2 of 2 copies), July; 1 (Box 72, Item barcode 39002104888103)
    - Empty folders (Box AV, Folder 847-854)
    - Cassette 7-8 Barger case, undated; 1 (Box 72, Item barcode 39002104888111)
      Transcript: File 52: 1-18, stored in: box 49, folder 939
    - Plot Tape 1: Levy's review with Larry Shears of taped phone conversations concerning Fresno slide, 1972 February 9; 1 (Box 72, Item barcode 39002104888129)
      Transcript: File 38 and 39: 162-233, stored in: box 47, folders 915 and 916
    - Plot Tape 2: Levy interview of Larry Shears in San Francisco, review of taped phone conversations, 1972 April 5; 1 (Box 72, Item barcode 39002104888137)
      Transcript: File 40: 495-546 stored in Box 47, folders 918-919
    - Plot Tape 3: Shears polygraph and interview, 1972 April 13; 1 (Box 72, Item barcode 39002104888145)
      Transcript: File 40: 594-641, stored in: box 47, folder 920
    - Plot Tape 4: Shears polygraph test, 1972 April 15; 1 (Box 72, Item barcode 39002104888152)
      Transcript: File 40: 642-656, stored in: box 47, folder 920
    - [Plot Tape 5]: Levy's review with Larry Shears of taped phone conversations, Levy's indexing of tapes, 1972 April 15; 1 (Box 72, Item barcode 39002104888160)
      Transcript: File 57, stored in box 49, folder 944. No transcript for side B
    - [Plot Tape 6]: Levy's review with Larry Shears of taped phone conversations, 1972 February 9; 1 (Box 72, Item barcode 39002104888178)
      Transcript: File 39: 234-322, stored in box 47, folders 916-917
    - [Plot Tape 7]: Levy interview of Larry Shears, undated; 1 (Box 72, Item barcode 39002104888186)
      Transcript: File 56: Shears Tape 3, stored in: box 49, folder 943
    - Plot Tape 8: BNE interview of Shears (1 of 3 copies), 1972 February 28; 1 (Box 73, Item barcode 39002104887246)
      2nd partial copy labeled "Cassette 3-4. Andy" and another continuation labeled "Cassette 5-6 Slote BNE." Transcript: File 40: 547-593, stored in box 47, folder 919. Side 6 of cassette 5-6 is blank
    - Cassette 3-4, Andy interview (2 of 3 copies), [1972 February 28]; 1 (Box 73, Item barcode 39002104887253)
      Copies include Plot Tape 8: BNE Interview of Shears and another continuation labeled "Cassette 5-6 Slote BNE." Transcript: File 40: 547-593, stored in box 47, folder 919. Side 6 of cassette 5-6 is blank
    - Cassette 5-6 Slote BNE (3 of 3 copies), [1972 February 28]; 1 (Box 73, Item barcode 39002104887261)
      Copies include Plot Tape 8: BNE Interview of Shear and 2nd partial copy labeled "Cassette 3-4. Andy" Transcript: File 40: 547-593, stored in box 47, folder 919. Side 6 of cassette 5-6 is blank
    - Cassette 3. Levy interview of Larry Shears, [1972 February 9]; 1 (Box 73, Item barcode 39002104887279)
      Transcript: file 54: 1-52, stored in box 49, folder 941
    - Cassette 6. JEL's compilation tape of Shears' phone conversations, tapes 1, 2, 3, and 6, undated; 1 (Box 73, Item barcode 39002104887287)
  - BOOK MATERIAL
    - File 1: Book Material I: Working Outline, 1972, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 866-868)
    - File 2: Book Material II, 1972, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 869-872)
    - File 3: Book Material III: Leftover Material, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 873-875)
    - File 3: Book Material III: Leftover Material, continued, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 876-877)
    - File 4: Cesar Chavez Plot Manuscript, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 878)
    - File 5: Index Strips I, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 879)
    - File 6: Index Strips II, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 880)
    - File 7: Index Strips III, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 881)
    - File 8: Index Strips IV, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 882)
    - File 9: Manuscript of Plot I, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 883)
    - File 10: Manuscript of Plot II, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 884)
    - File 11: Manuscript of Plot III, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 885-886)
  - PLOT FILES
    - File 12: Blue Notebook Index (Box 45, Folder 887)
    - File 13: Correspondence, 1971-72 (Box 45, Folder 888)
    - File 14: Cover-up, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 889)
    - File 15: Facts on Plot, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 890)
    - File 16: Federal and Local Law Enforcement (Box 45, Folder 891)
    - File 17: JEL Notes, 1971-72 (Box 45, Folder 892)
    - File 18: JEL Notes: Memos on Conversations, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 893)
    - File 19: JEL Notes: Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 894)
    - File 20: JEL Notes: Questions, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 895)
    - File 21: JEL Notes: Robinson & Nixon of ATF Interview, 1973 Dec (Box 46, Folder 896)
    - File 22: Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 897)
    - File 23: News Stories, 1971-72, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 898)
    - File 24: Richard Pedigo, 1972, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 899)
    - File 25: Pedigo-Sandrini Court Transcript, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 900)
    - File 26: Persons, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 901)
    - File 27: Plot Story, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 902)
    - File 28: Polygraph of Larry Shears, 1972, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 903)
    - File 29: Prochnau, Buddy Gene, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 904)
    - File 30: Publishing Material, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 905)
    - File 31: Rolling Stone, 1972, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 906)
    - File 32: Shears, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 907)
    - File 33: Shears Story, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 908)
    - File 34: Younger, Evelle, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 909)
  - PLOT MATERIAL
    - File 35: ATF Index (Box 46, Folder 910)
    - File 36: Contents Listing of Plot Material, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 911)
    - File 37: Person Index (Box 46, Folder 912)
    - File 38: Plot Material: 1-199, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 913-915)
    - File 39: Plot Material: 200-405, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 916-917)
    - File 40: Plot Material: 406-663, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 918-920)
    - File 41: Plot Material Duplicate, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 921)
  - SHEARS TAPES
    - File 42: Brief Summary of Shears Tapes, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 922)
    - File 43: Shears Tapes: 1-26, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 923-925)
    - File 44: Shears Tapes: 27-40, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 926-928)
    - File 45: Shears Tapes: 29-40, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 929-931)
  - THE SNITCH
    - File 46: "The Snitch" Screenplay, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 932-933)
  - TRANSCRIPTS
    - File 47: LeRoy Anderson, Lt. (Box 49, Folder 934)
    - File 48: Cesar Chavez Phone Calls, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 935)
    - File 49: Rex Davis, Director of ATF, Interview, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 936)
    - File 50: Mrs. Pedigo Phone Call, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 937)
    - File 51: Prochnau Press Conference, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 938)
    - File 52: Shears: 1, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 939)
    - File 53: Shears: 2, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 940)
    - File 54: Shears: 3, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 941)
    - File 55: Shears, Pedigo, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 942)
    - File 56: Shears Tape 3, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 943)
    - File 57: Shears Tape 3x, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 944)
    - File 58: Jann Wenner Phone Calls, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 945)
- Oversize, 4.26; (3 boxes) + 4 broadside folders
  Oversize contains material from Series V, VI, and VII, and is organized in box order.
  - Clippings Prior to 1969 (from Series V) (Box 50, Folder 946)
  - 1969 Clippings (from Series V), 1969, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 947)
  - 1970 Clippings (from Series V), 1970, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 948-950)
  - 1971 Clippings (from Series V), 1971, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 951)
  - 1972 Clippings (from Series V), 1972, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 952)
  - 1973 Clippings: clipping numbers 823 to 1124 (from Series V), 1973, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 953)
  - 1973 Clippings: clipping numbers 1125 to 1624 (from Series V), 1973, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 954-956)
  - 1974 Clippings (from Series V), 1974, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 957)
  - 1975 Clippings (from Series V), 1975, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 958)
  - 1976-1996 Clippings (from Series V), 1976-96, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 959)
  - Undated Articles (from Series V) (Box 51, Folder 960)
  - UFW Collected Clipping Sheets (from Series V), 1975-76, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 961-964)
  - File 1 CALRA: NLRA (from Series VI), 1968 (Box 51, Folder 965)
  - File 18 CALRA: Prop. 22 (from Series VI) (Box 51, Folder 966)
  - File 35: Teamster Literature (from Series VI), 1975, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 967)
  - File 60: Press Clips (from Series VI), 1969-75, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 968)
  - File 61: Press Clips (from Series VI), 1975 Apr-May, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 969)
  - File 62: Press Clips (from Series VI), 1975 May, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 970)
  - File 63: Press Clips (from Series VI), 1975-76, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 971)
  - File 64: Additional Press Clippings (from Series VI), 1974-76, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 972)
  - File 51. Chris Hartmire Enneagram (from Series VII), 1994 (Box 51, Folder 973)
  - File 75. Cesar Chavez Memorial Poster (from Series VII), [1993] (Box 51, Folder 974)
  - File 79. PMR News Clippings (from Series VII), 1993-96, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 975)
  - File 76. Dolores Huerta (from Series VII), 1988 (Box 52, Folder 976-977)
  - 1970 Clippings (from Series V), 1970, n.d. (Box bsd, folder 978)
  - 1973 Clippings: clipping numbers 823 to 1124 (from Series V), 1973, n.d. (Box bsd, folder 979)
  - 1973 Clippings: clipping numbers 1125 to 1624 (from Series V), 1973, n.d. (Box bsd, folder 980)
  - File 71. Timeline Chart (from Series VII), n.d. (Box bsd, folder 981)
- Restricted Fragile, 9.25; (3 boxes) + 1 broadside folder
  Boxes 74-76, Restricted Fragile, contains audiovisual material. Restricted fragile. The material is arranged in folder order and may only be seen with the permission of the appropriate curator. Preservation photocopies have been substituted in the main files for reference use.
  - AV, original cassette shells (Box 74, Folder 1004)
  - Box 17, folder 362 (Box 75, Folder 1005)
  - Box 17, folder 363 (Box 75, Folder 1006)
  - Box 17, folder 375 (Box 75, Folder 1007)
  - Box 18, folder 377 (Box 75, Folder 1008)
  - Box 18, folder 379 (Box 75, Folder 1009)
  - Box 18, folder 385 (Box 75, Folder 1010)
  - Box 19, folder 403 (Box 75, Folder 1011)
  - Box 19, folder 412 (Box 75, Folder 1012)
  - Box 19, folder 413 (Box 75, Folder 1013)
  - Box 20, folder 423 (Box 75, Folder 1014)
  - Box 20, folder 427 (Box 75, Folder 1015)
  - Box 21, folder 446 (Box 75, Folder 1016)
  - Box 21, folder 460 (Box 75, Folder 1017)
  - Box 21, folder 461 (Box 75, Folder 1018)
  - Box 22, folder 467 (Box 75, Folder 1019)
  - Box 33, folder 692 (Box 75, Folder 1020)
  - Box 37, folder 730 (Box 75, Folder 1021)
  - Box 38, folder 762 (Box 75, Folder 1022)
  - Box 38, folder 768 (Box 75, Folder 1023)
  - Box 38, folder 769 (Box 75, Folder 1024)
  - Box 41, folder 783 (Box 75, Folder 1025)
  - Box 41, folder 789 (Box 75, Folder 1026)
  - Box 41, folder 792 (Box 75, Folder 1027)
  - Box 41, folder 793 (Box 75, Folder 1028)
  - Box 41, folder 794 (Box 75, Folder 1029)
  - Box 41, folder 796 (Box 75, Folder 1030)
  - Box 41, folder 797 (Box 75, Folder 1031)
  - Box 41, folder 798 (Box 75, Folder 1032)
  - Box 42, folder 817 (Box 75, Folder 1033)
  - Box 18, folder 381 (Box 76, Folder 1034)